BRIDGET MAHY



NEW ZEALAND CITIZEN



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hello! I recently finished a coding bootcamp with Dev Academy NZ and I am excited to bring my skills to your workplace in Melbourne. My transition to web development was driven by a fascination with contemporary trends, internet culture and a passion for continuous learning and problem-solving. Collaborating on web development projects has been immensely rewarding as it allows me to witness firsthand how the communication and critical thinking skills I gained from my humanities study translate into a modern environment in the production of high-quality concise code. My curiosity for emerging trends means that I stay up-to-date with the latest web technologies and enjoy incorporating them into my work. In my spare time I love reading, watching movies and doing yoga to keep me balanced.

CONTACT

- +64 22-623-8703
- ☑ bridget.mahy@gmail.com
- bridgets-portfolio.vercel.app
- ♠ Christchurch, NZ

EDUCATION

Level 6 Certificate - Applied Software Development

Dev Academy Aotearoa

Bachelor of Arts - Art History 2019 - 2021

Victoria University of Wellington

GPA 7.09/8

Deans List 2020, 2021

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Typescript, React, Git, Knex, Redux, Node, Tailwind, Express, Next, Auth0, Jest.

REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST

EXPERIENCE

Dev Academy

Trainee

Feb 2023 - May 2023

With only a basic understanding of HTML and CSS, I launched into this intensive 17 week bootcamp, developing proficiency in full stack development (within a fast-paced environment) through agile-facilitated group projects and paired programming challenges. The program prioritized soft skills, refining my feedback, conflict resolution, and presentation skills. In a social media test-driven development project called Kes-Ke-Say, I worked in a pair to produce a page for viewing chat groups achieving 100% test coverage over our code. In the last section of bootcamp I was the product owner of an app called Gallerina that I had pitched to my cohort. In this role, I demonstrated leadership skills by working closely with my team to generate a feasible MVP and by guiding the vision for the project throughout it's development. I helped produce the page for viewing collections and a single collection. I deployed the website and coded the search page as well as the external api calls for the арр.

City Gallery Wellington

Gallery Assistant

Dec 2021 - Oct 2022

I developed my public-facing communication skills by greeting visitors to the gallery and fielding their queries about the exhibitions on display. Additionally, I learned to be assertive in a professional and respectful manner when visitors needed guidance on how to interact with the artwork, ensuring the safety and preservation of the pieces.

OPSM Lambton Quay

Optical Assistant

Dec 2021 - Aug 2022

In this role I strengthened my organisational intuition by managing appointment bookings, processing shipped orders, dispensing glasses to customers and managing end-of-day banking in a busy store at the centre of the business district.